ciena.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Use - Ciena

This privacy policy (the Policy) sets out how we, at Ciena, collect, use and protect your personal information.

We can collect your personal information when you:

  * browse our web site(s);
  * subscribe to our alerts and publications (including newsletters and mailing lists);
  * request information from us about products and services;
  * contact us with a question or complaint;
  * visit us at various industry events

**Collecting & Using Personal Information**

The information we may collect includes, but isn’t limited to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. You can use our website without divulging any personal information. We do not collect personal information about you unless you expressly provide such information to us on a voluntary basis, for example, when registering or logging into our Support Center, subscribing to our investor distribution or one of our publications, or requesting more information to be sent to you about Ciena. We will only use your personal information for the purposes that you have provided it for or consented to.

We may also add the information you provide to our databases, subscriber lists and/or contact lists for general marketing purposes. When you submit personal information to you understand and consent to the transfer of your personal information to other companies within the Ciena group, which may include transfers across national borders and the storage and processing of your information in a country that may not provide privacy protections similar to those your country provides. Where such transfers are made, we ensure that the receiving party treats your personal information in accordance with this Policy and applicable law.

**Our commitment to data security**

To prevent unauthorized access and misuse of your personal information (including accidental loss, disclosure, alteration or destruction), maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate technical, organizational, administrative, physical and procedural security measures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect from you as described in this Policy.

We do not rent, sell, or share the personal information we collect about you with third parties or non-affiliated companies, unless we are required to by law, or in response to a government investigation.

To the extent that third parties assist Ciena in the provision of our website(s) or services offered on our website(s) (or otherwise), those third parties have no independent rights to your personal information, we make sure they have appropriate protections in place for your personal information, and only process your personal information in the way we have permitted them to.

**Non-Personal and aggregated information collected automatically**

When you visit our website, we log general data, such as your domain name, the name of the web page from which you entered our website, which pages you visit on our website, and how much time you spend on each page. We use this information to monitor use of and improve our website as well as for internal analysis. In particular, we use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the website, and gather information for aggregate use (IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information).

**Use of Cookies**

Our website uses "cookies" to help personalize your online experience, such as recognizing repeat visitors. A cookie is a text file that is anonymously placed on your hard disk by a web page server. This site's cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Ciena does not match your personally identifiable information with the cookie assigned to you. We will not share or sell non-aggregated information contained within cookies with any third party. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of our website or receive some of our services.

**External links**

Ciena may provide links to external web sites for your convenience. The links and information these sites contain are not monitored by us and those sites are subject to their own privacy policies. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy or practices of these sites nor do we endorse these sites or content provide thereon.

**Changes to the Policy**

The date set out at the end of this Policy indicates the date it was last updated. We may occasionally amend this Policy to reflect company and customer feedback and any changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation.

We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to be informed of how we are committed to protecting your information and providing you with improved content on our website. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share the personal information that you have voluntarily provided, we will notify you by posting notice of the changes at this Policy. By using this website, you signify your agreement with the terms of this Privacy.

**Questions about our privacy policy and contacting Ciena**

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us by email at: [privacypolicy@ciena.com](mailto:privacypolicy@ciena.com). Or by writing to Ciena at:

Ciena Corporation  
ATTN: Director of Digital Marketing  
7035 Ridge Road, Hanover, Maryland 21076, USA

If you wish to unsubscribe or discontinue receiving communications from us (including newsletters and other materials) please use the unsubscibe facility/preference center link provided [here](http://mynetwork.ciena.com/Preferences.html). If you wish to update your information, please contact us by email at [privacypolicy@ciena.com](mailto:privacypolicy@ciena.com) or at the contact information above.

**European Union**

If you are resident in the European Union, for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other relevant data protection or privacy legislation, Ciena is the Data Controller of your personal data. You have the right to ask Ciena for a copy of your personal data; to correct, delete or restrict processing of your personal data; and to obtain the personal data you provide to us in a structured, machine readable format. You have the right to withdraw your consent to our use of your personal data at any time. If you have unresolved concerns, you have the right to complain to the relevant data protection authority in your EU Member State.

**Legal Notice**

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Ciena” means Ciena Corporation, and any company or other entity which Ciena Corporation owns (directly or indirectly) 100% of the issued share capital. If the business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchaser’s adviser(s) and will be passed to the new owners of the business. Where required by local law, you will be informed of such transfers.

_May 2018_
